Xavier University Futures Committee records
Xavier University Archives and Special Collections
Xavier University Futures Committee records
1988-1991
Xavier University Archives and Special Collections Phone: 513-745-4821 http://www.xavier.edu/cm/archives
Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Futures Committee
1.3 linear feet (3 boxes)
Records of the Xavier University Futures Committee which existed from 1988 to 1991. The collection includes some meeting minutes, reports, correspondence, memos and related documents.
XUA-15
History of the Xavier University Futures Committee
On December 5, 1988, the president of Xavier University, Albert J. DiUlio, S.J., established a committee which he named the "Futures Committee." Its task, as the president explained, was "to articulate a direction, set priorities and develop a plan for implementing these for Xavier between now and the year 2000." The Futures Committee completed its work and submitted its final report to DiUlio's successor, James. E. Hoff, S.J., in the spring of 1991. The final report was published and distributed to the Xavier community in July, 1991. Although self-described as a standing committee, it went out of existence upon the completion of its task.
Not specified
Scope and Content
Records resulting from the activities of the Xavier University Futures Committee. Records include meeting minutes, reports, surveys, letters, memos and related documents.
Not specified
Statement of Arrangement
Meeting minutes and related materials are arranged chronologically into folders. Committee documents (including the final report) are arranged following the meeting minutes and are also arranged chronologically.
Restrictions on Access
Restricted access. Please contact the Xavier University Archives staff.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Subjects:
Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio)--Planning
Detailed Description of The Collection
- Futures Committee Background Material, 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Futures Committee Preparatory Materials, 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Futures Committee Papers, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Futures Committee Papers, 1989 March-June (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Futures Committee Papers, 1989 June-August (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Futures Committee Papers, 1989 August-September (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Futures Committee Papers, 1989 October-December (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Futures Committee Papers, 1990 January-March (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Futures Committee Papers, 1990 March-April (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Futures Committee Papers, 1990 April-June (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Futures Committee Papers, 1990 July-September (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Futures Committee Papers, 1990 September-November (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Futures Committee Papers, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Futures Committee Papers, 1991 January-July (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Futures Committee Environmental Assessment, 1989 September (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Futures Committee Environmental Assessment, 1989 September (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Futures Committee Working Vision, First Draft, 1990 March (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Futures Committee Proposal for Future, 1991 March (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Futures Committee Proposal for the Future, Final Report, 1991 July (Box 3, Folder 19)